Finding aid for the Jerry Lewis papers LSC.2124
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Series 4: Media, 1961-2012
  - Photos: Jerry Lewis with Dan Quayle, 1991 (Box 80, Folder 5)
  - Photos: Jerry Lewis with Nixon and Reagan, 1983-2004 (Box 80, Folder 6)
  - Photos: Negatives, Contact Sheets, 1972-1975 (Box 81, Folder 1)
  - Photos: Negatives, Contact Sheets, 1972-1975 (Box 81, Folder 2)
  - Photos: Negatives, Contact Sheets, 1978-1985 (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - Photos: Negatives, Contact Sheets, 1978-1990 (Box 81, Folder 4)
  - Photos: Negatives, Contact Sheets, 1978-1990 (Box 81, Folder 5)
  - Photos: Negatives, 1980 (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - Photos: Negatives, Slides, 1981-1990 (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - Photos: Negatives, Slides, 1988-2000 (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - Photos: Office Photos, 1979-2012 (Box 82, Folder 4)
  - Photos: Photos From 1996, 2007 (Box 82, Folder 5)
  - Photos: Photos From 2007 (Box 82, Folder 6)
  - Photos: Presidents Bush and Clinton, Volume 1, 1988-2000 (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - Photos: Presidents Bush and Clinton, Volume 1, 1988-2000 (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - Photos: Presidents Bush and Clinton, Volume 2, 1989-2000 (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - Photos: Presidents Bush and Clinton, Volume 2, 1989-2000 (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - Photos, circa 1970s (Box 89, Folder 1)
  - Photos, circa 1980s-2000s (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - Photos, undated (Box 89, Folder 3)
  - Photos, 1980s (Box 89, Folder 4)
  - Photos, undated (Box 89, Folder 5)
  - Photos, undated (Box 89, Folder 6)
  - Photos, undated (Box 89, Folder 7)
  - Photos, undated (Box 90, Folder 1)
  - Photos, 1980s (Box 90, Folder 2)
  - Photos, 1980s (Box 90, Folder 3)
  - Photos, 1970-2001 (Box 90, Folder 4)
- Series 5: Electronic calendar print outs, budget requests, and CDs, 1996-2009
  - Printed electronic calendar: 1996 (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - Printed electronic calendar: 1998 (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - Printed electronic calendar: 1999 (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - Printed electronic calendar: 2000 (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - Printed electronic calendar: 2001 (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - Printed electronic calendars: 2002, 2003, 2005, 2006, 2002-2006 (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - Printed electronic calendar: 2002 (Box 86, Folder 2-3)
  - Printed electronic calendar: 2003 (Box 86, Folder 4)
  - Printed electronic calendar: 2004 (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - Printed electronic calendar: 2005 (Box 87, Folder 2)
  - Printed electronic calendar: 2006 (Box 87, Folder 3)
  - Printed electronic calendar: 2005 (Box 88, Folder 1)
  - Printed electronic calendar: 2006 (Box 88, Folder 2)
  - Printed electronic calendar: 2007 (Box 88, Folder 3)
  - Printed electronic calendar: 2008 (Box 88, Folder 4)
  - Printed electronic calendar: 2009 (Box 88, Folder 5)
  - Budget requests, undated (Box 88, Folder 6)
  - CDs, circa 2000s (Box 88, Folder 7)